okay so one of the great things about
Haack is we don't just have people from
the industry side here we have people
from the academic side and our next
speaker is Shan Maven have I pronounced
that right marvelous um he's uh
currently at the University of Glasgow
where he's a lecturer an assistant
professor and he a researcher developing
new techniques for using AI in search
engines um and he's going to be talking
about rethinking reranking so without
further Ado Sean
mavet uh hello everybody um thank you
for the for the lovely introduction I'm
Sean mcavaney uh I'm a new face around
here uh I don't recognize uh recognize
many of you and I'm sure uh I'm a new
face to you guys too so uh just a little
bit of uh little bit of background on
myself um as uh as was introduced I'm
Sean mcavan you can find me on Twitter
or x with my with my surname there um uh
I'm a uh lecturer assistant professor at
the University of Glasgow uh and my
research mostly focuses on uh very
practical oriented research within
information retrieval uh so if you've
heard of techniques like learn sparse
expansion the kind of thing that Slade
uses in order to uh to add uh tokens to
documents or queries uh things like
search results evaluation using large
language models you don't have to do as
much uh as much labeling document
quality prediction so you uh don't need
to index garbage um and uh the topic of
today's talk uh which is uh which is
adaptive
reranking I'm happy to chat with uh with
you about any of these topics or or
other things as
well um let's start off talking a little
bit about about what we ranking is we
had a we had a nice introduction ear
today on on a lot of the the pipelines
and processes that you can go through um
but I want to I want to take a little
bit of a a separate Twist on this by by
kind of rethinking this whole
process uh so typically what uh what a
reranking system would look like first
you would have some user query user
enters in tablet or something into the
search engine uh you run your retriever
maybe that's bm25 for lexical search or
Fanci or vector methods uh to get some
list of results over your data set and
this is a an okay ranking but maybe not
maybe not so great all the time right so
uh especially if you're doing something
like lexical search uh there can there
can be a lot of problems in uh in how
these results are are ranked um so what
you'll often want to do is you'll often
want to use a ranker something that uses
a model like Bert or GPT uh or anything
like that uh in order to hopefully find
a better order for the search results uh
and hopefully at the end of that you get
some new awesome ranking of these
results right so using our fancy large
language models and so forth you're able
to uh really understand the content of
uh of documents really understand the
intent of the query hopefully uh uh and
put these documents in a much better
order now there's a problem with this
process though uh you start off with
millions and millions of documents you
narrow that down you filter that down to
maybe hundreds of documents and then you
essentially use the ranker to pick what
top 10 documents or so you you end up
showing the user
but if you miss a document when doing
retrieving you start off with millions
of documents and and you miss this this
golden document here that that doesn't
quite meet the filter uh you'll never
have it down here to rerank right you
lose it completely right um you know if
it's a product that you're searching for
you never get
it uh to address this problem people
have have thought about all all sorts of
solutions and and the typical go-to
place to address this uh recall problem
as as you would call it uh is to focus
on the R it's a natural place to look
the the retriever misses something so
you want to fix the retriever so it
doesn't miss those things come up with
all sorts of great approaches for for
doing the sense retrieval learn sparse
fybrid etc etc etc in order to try to
try to enhance this pool of documents uh
that the rerer gets that you don't miss
uh what you're really looking
for now what I would argue is is really
what we wish we could do is we wish we
could run the ranker just as a ranker
over the entire Corpus right we have
millions of documents we really trust
you know maybe GPT 40 Mini's uh
assessment of uh of search result
quality we really would like to score
every single document and then we would
for sure get that gold document at the
top no matter what uh assuming it's the
best document and your ranker is able to
identify
that uh of course this is just way too
costly um uh obviously um you know doing
all this uh doing all this inference it
cost a lot of time if you're using GPT
for it would cost a lot of API credits
and and so
on now the next best best best option I
would argue uh is to give the ranker
access not just to the list of uh of
initial search results that you get from
your retriever uh but also access to the
whole rest of your data set the whole
rest of your
corpus now this seems like the same
thing as this right um but actually uh
kind of leveraging this initial set of
results is super super powerful in order
to kind of unlock uh a lot of the other
documents in your
Corpus it seems crazy uh but I'll show
you how this can done uh can be done
with minimal cost uh so basically with
uh essentially no extra
cost um how it can uh not just improve
reranking methods uh you know like using
gp4 or whatever uh but also uh
retrievers like Co bear and others and
uh and on top of that it's uh it's ready
to use with open source tools and so
forth uh for you to to start using today
if you like
like I promise I'm going something where
with uh some somewhere with this uh but
let's talk about the game Battleship uh
who who knows the game Battleship yes
seems like seems like most everybody
that's good um uh I asked I asked around
a little bit and in German it's shiffer
shenen um and uh in uh in Spanish it
translates to sync the fleet uh anyway
hopefully you you have some familiarity
with this game
um I used to play it uh as as a child
it's kind of fun uh basically the idea
is that you're playing against opponent
who has a secret board right where they
have a bunch of ships you know that uh
you know they have some long ships and
some short ships uh all laid out on on
kind of this coordinate grid uh but of
course you don't you don't see that
board right your board starts off
completely empty right so you don't know
where the ships are but your goal is to
identify the positions of all your
opponent ships right so you want to
figure out that uh you know for instance
the the long ship there is uh from uh
what B2 to B5 and so
forth the way that you do this uh is you
first just make a guess right this might
be a reasonable guess you don't really
know anything about uh about your
opponent's board initially so you you
make a guess you ask your opponent then
uh is this a hit right so it's as if
you're you're you're launching a strike
into the ocean for some reason you don't
actually have any intelligence about the
actual positions of the ship but let's
ignore that uh that limitation of the
game um you ask your opponent uh if it's
a hit uh it turns out this one is a Miss
uh there's no ship
there maybe then you make another guess
and that happens to be a hit so you ask
your opponent uh you know F2 is that a
hit yes it is a
hit now once you know that that's a hit
uh the way the game works at least you
don't s syn the Shimp immediately uh you
need to guess all the positions of of
the ship and at this point you actually
learn a lot about where the ship might
be right um you know that they can only
be oriented kind of vertically or
horizontally uh so you know that the
ship there's uh absolutely certainly uh
one of the other positions of the ship
is is in one of these coordinates with
the with the question mark at this
point so maybe you guess one of them
that happens to be a miss you guess
another one Ah that's another hit and
then you kind of iterate on this process
to find the uh find the complete uh
complete
ship okay so what does this what does
this have to do with
ranking well I would argue uh that when
you're doing uh when you're doing
reranking when you're doing uh reranking
you essentially think of these uh these
initial list of results that you get
reasonable guesses as kind of uh guesses
on this uh on this board right uh so
maybe you have documents one two and
three at at these particular
positions and instead of asking you know
your opponent if uh if a a if your
document is a hit or a Miss uh you're
asking your ranker right you're you're
saying is this a good document is this a
bad document where does this go in the
ranking and your ranker gives you know
some uh some new information right so
maybe this document up there at position
C7 uh that's now the first top ranks
document that's a really good document
for this query and this one over here at
E5 is is not so
great now what's crazy to me is that in
in normal reranking you just stop right
here right you learn all this stuff
about which documents are good and which
are bad uh and then you just show these
to the user right uh if I was playing
Battleship right now that would be a
terrible strategy right I would I would
basically miss all the ships if I wanted
to find all the positions I would need
to just keep on guessing randomly until
I find all of
them so uh we've actually learned a lot
of information about what makes a
document relevant to this query right uh
by identifying a query that sorry by
identifying a document that is relevant
that's considered relevant by some
really strong uh really strong model
like like
gp24 adaptive reranking uh is this uh is
this approach uh where we kind of
Leverage this information that we gained
from these high-scoring documents to
find other ones that were missed by the
retriever so we don't necessarily need
these documents to come back in that
first set of guesses we just need
something that gets as roughly close and
we can kind of then explore explore the
area around it so maybe we send these
four other documents that are adjacent
to our fancy reranking method some of
them are are not so good right you know
we're just kind of using the proximity
here to kind of guess what what might be
a good document what might be a bad
document but we find another one and
that kind of gives us even more
information about what's good and we
iterate that process so on and so
forth does that make sense
yeah okay uh the next question is how do
we decide which documents are worth
checking right so when we have a
coordinate system in uh in Battleship
right we uh you know there's uh
characteristics about the shapes of the
ships that uh that we can leverage we
know things about how uh you know the
lengths of the ships and how they must
be kind of oriented in on the game board
uh in uh in ranking we don't we don't
have that exactly uh but we have
something similar uh so one option would
be to once we kind of identify a
document that we think is really good uh
we could issue that same document as a
query back to our engine and take the
top results for that query right uh so
we treat this this document that we have
as a query and find the most similar
other documents to it if this is a good
document documents that are similar to
that are probably also good uh this goes
to a bunch of ir Theory um from Van rice
Bergen and deals with the cluster
hypothesis and so on but uh in in a
practical sense uh the idea is that a a
similar document or sorry a document
similar to the one that you think is
good might also be good we don't know
for sure but we'll use the ranker to
tell us if it's actually
good this is a really really bad idea um
it's uh it's it's really slow uh you
don't want to have to actually execute
you know look up your your document
maybe even encode it as a you know new
query executed against the engine all
that uh really bad really slow that's a
terrible idea you know won't be
practical in the slightest um but it is
still the right idea um at at least in
my opinion right because uh you're able
to kind of Leverage the information that
you get from this document and say you
know I I want documents that are kind of
along this line right I think this is a
really good results but but what are the
others the other good ones
there uh what can we do better uh well
we can Leverage is something we actually
already have at least in uh in most
Vector databases uh we can leverage this
uh kir neighbor graph uh that we've
built for doing Vector search for using
hnsw search we already have this graph
that says you know here's a document
here a similar document to this and we
already use this to do uh to do search
over vectors right um this graph kind of
already establishes this proximity it's
as if it's that coordinate system from
Battleship um it's super fast lookups
right so uh you're able to immediately
you know just by your your document
identifier able to see you know these
other six documents or 100 documents or
however you said it uh are similar or
related to this and it's constructed
completely offline so you're not really
incurring any costs at query time right
right you already have the STA structure
ready to
go all right so that's the idea how well
does it actually work um first a few
technical bits um you know being a
scientist I got a caveat with with all
this stuff right um we do things like
fixed the r ranking what we call the
budget which is the number of documents
that we're sending to the ranker so uh
we're not comparing a A system that
ranks 100 documents with one that ranks
a thousand something like that no all of
these systems are ranking the same
number of results so that cost is fixed
um in our adaptive setting uh we just
take a really simple approach of taking
basically half the results from the
first stage and augmenting it with uh
the other half of results that we'll
score uh from this proximity graph right
so we look up the best documents and
kind of iterate on that
process in terms of you know does it
work uh we'll measure ndcg for the
overall ranking quality and recall which
is uh in this case the percentage of
relevant documents
retrieved and we test on a variety of
different uh reranking pipelines
reranking
systems okay uh so here we have a here
we have a graph we have recall recall a
thousand on the on the x-axis there so
how many of the relevant documents have
we found and ndcg on the y- axis and
here's just a set of initial retrievers
right so we have bm25 there with lexical
search uh we have an augmented bm25
called doc to query uh we have TCT which
is a vector search and we have Spade
version 2++ XYZ whatever um up there uh
very very strong right it's getting high
recall and very good search
results now putting a ranker on top of
this right let's try reranking our
electrical search results our bm25
search results using a reranking model
here we're using monot T5 but we tested
this across a whole bunch of different
ones and as you would expect when doing
just regular reranking uh it improves
the overall search result quality a ton
right ndcg improves substantially right
from what 6 to 73 right that's a that's
a pretty big jump you're getting a lot
more of the best results at the top of
the list um but recall doesn't change
right it's a vertical line right uh
you're not finding any new documents
that uh that you had
before when you apply this adaptive
approach on top of that you shoot all
the way over there right so uh not only
are you improving further improving the
the overall quality of the top result
but you're finding a lot whole lot more
uh of the relevant documents for this
query and what's actually quite
remarkable is the recall is doing better
than something like a vector search
would right by kind of leveraging the uh
leveraging your cross encoder leveraging
your ranker to try to find the best
results uh you're you're doing better
than you would have uh had you done some
fancy semantic search to begin with
still not quite atplay um but of course
you can also run reranking on top of any
of these other syst systems right so you
can uh rerank and adaptively rerank on
all of those too and you see pretty
consistent results in terms of uh
improving the uh the overall search
result quality and uh and the overall
efficiency and this isn't reranking kind
of any uh uh it's not like you're
reranking a thousand documents when you
previously R ranking a 100 right the
costs are are basically fixed right
you're still reranking the same number
of documents you're just being smarter
about which documents you're reranking
and the process of looking up these
documents is is really really cheap
right it's all computed offline so the
cost is basically fixed across all of
these um this isn't just on uh this
doesn't just work on uh you know weird
academic monot T5 rankers uh I tried it
on coher uh cross encoder model when
they released one a while back and yeah
we see similar similar situation right
so oh that not so visible uh uh on this
display but we can see ndcg is
increasing calls increasing
Etc all right so in summary there uh we
found that kind of this nearest neighbor
graph exploration really helps reranking
models um neural reranking models and by
focusing the ne uh on the neighbors of
the top scoring documents as we're
ranking like we're playing Battleship
right finding the the similar positions
to the ones we already know are good uh
this helps prioritize documents that are
more likely to actually be
relevant we have a whole bunch of other
findings and stuff and there's a
conference paper on it um uh if uh if
you want to if you want to
read okay let's go on to retrievers
let's talk about retrieving retriever
models so the Adaptive approach that I
was uh I was talking about up to this
point it actually involves two
strategies we focused mostly on this
this first part so scoring documents
near the best ones we found so far
that's essentially the the Adaptive bit
of adaptive reranking
the second bit and I was it was a little
subtle about this before but now it's
really important um is the reranking bit
it says we're going to start off with
good uh but really inexpensive guesses
about what uh what are uh what are good
documents so we're not just randomly
guessing on the uh on the board of for
for Battleship right we have some good
guesses about where the ships might be
right where the good good relevant
documents
are so uh the intuition of the of the
next part of this talk is is can we
leverage the same strategy starting with
good but cheap guesses uh can this also
help DSE retrieval models and it turns
out they
can so um hnsw uh hopefully you're all
you're all familiar with this this is
one of the approximate nearest neighbor
algorithms and it's commonly deployed in
a whole bunch of different different
engines um hsw actually kind of applies
this this random strategy uh as if you
were just kind of randomly picking on
your uh on your battleship board right
uh you randomly uh subsample nodes from
from one version of your uh hierar graph
to the next to the next and then you
search kind of uh the opposite way back
down so you start off essentially
searching and scoring random documents
and kind of iterating on this process to
find slightly better and better
documents as you go uh until you're kind
of at the lowest level and then you find
the the most similar results there so H
sub kind of takes this uh takes this
random approach right as if you're just
kind of randomly guessing and then
narrowing In from from
there can we leverage uh instead uh this
initial cheap set of of search results
that we can get with just a simple
lexical search uh for very uh very low
cost uh can we use this instead to kind
of help seed this search process right
so instead of navigating through this
hierarchical graph and looking at this
and looking at that and scoring all the
way down uh can we instead start off by
picking some of those nodes right so
uh the green and uh and blue don't show
up particularly well here but picking
some of these nodes here um and starting
off with uh with those uh to kind of
seed our search uh instead of the
hierarchical approach
instead and once we do that once we know
which documents are the best from this
initial pool of uh of results from
something like bm25 uh we're able to
then kind of iterate on that process to
continue to find better and better
documents so kind of shortcutting this
whole hierarchical approach of H s
w okay uh so how well does uh does this
approach work um well here now uh we're
uh we're most interested in uh in two
things uh on the y-axis we're interested
in the search overall search result
quality so ndcg and on the x-axis uh
retrieval latency so this is
milliseconds per query searching over
around 10 uh 10 million short
passages um this is a standard
information retrieval benchmark
uh a pretty standard um IND Den
retrieval model and this is using a
single core of a CPU so it's a single
threaded uh this this whole
process as a point of reference if we
did an exhaustive search on a GPU over
all these vectors uh something way more
expensive than a single core of a CPU uh
that would get us uh this line here uh
in around 65 milliseconds so beyond the
scope of this with way more
compute hnsw uh is is really strong uh
right so we're able in you know five six
milliseconds uh up to up to eight8
milliseconds to to do a really really
strong approximation of that uh of the
full results get very strong results of
uh uh in the top of our in the top of
our ranking and uh we can vary kind of
uh how long we're willing to uh to take
on this process by changing some of the
parameters of hnw that say how how much
of the graph you're willing to
explore there's other approaches too but
they don't work as well um now if we
just rerank so in our in our first talk
today we we heard about kind of this
reranking approach where you can uh take
bm25 and just rerank using uh uh using
our vectors instead that actually
eclipses hnsw in in most of these
settings uh just by choosing a different
number of uh of search results to rerank
uh so reranking itself is already really
strong and then if we do this adaptive
approach where we're looking at the
neighbors and prioritizing the neighbor
neighb uh and seeding kind of this uh
this search of our graph using the
neighbors instead uh that does even
better uh and it turns out that it can
do uh even better than an exhaustive
search right even better than scoring
everything we're finding more of the
best results uh for our
queries um we found that this doesn't
just work on these single uh
representation dense uh Den vectors uh
this also works on something like Co
bear so uh so at Sig this year we
presented this page paper uh where we
tested out using ladder uh compared it
with reranking and this algorithm called
plade which is this bespoke engine
specifically made for Co bear to try to
find kind of the best results uh and
again we see similar uh similar findings
to what we saw with the single Vector
representations we're able to do
substantially better basically at at any
operational point that we
choose okay uh so in summary on on the
second part uh adaptive reranking ideas
can improve retrievers too not just
rankers so uh rather than just focusing
on on these kind of expensive uh
language model reranking techniques uh
we able to leverage them kind of at uh
at the initial search side too to get uh
to get better results and it applies to
both single vector and uh multi Vector
dense retrieval models we've
seen of course other findings uh blah
blah blah conference papers you can uh
you can look at these if uh if you're
Keen okay uh on top of that uh these
techniques are open source and ready
ready to use uh so they're not just uh
an idea of an academic in a in an ivory
Tower or something like that uh uh these
are uh these are ready for you guys to
to use today if if you like um so uh we
have uh at the University of Glasgow we
have this platform called py Terrier uh
which kind of lets you glue together all
these different components in different
ways uh there is an Adaptive reranking
and Ladder component in py teror to let
you uh to let you play around with
that um it could also be used with the
rankers package uh so if you're familiar
with this from um an answer. is that it
um uh there's a there's this nice
package with re rankers you can use it
with that too um I've got a fork of
rankers but I'm going to make a PL
request at some point when I when I get
around to it so hopefully that makes
into the the core uh rankers package
there um we're working on adding uh
ladder to Lucine um the the Lucine
maintainers uh seem seem positive to it
uh but you know they're they can be a
bit picky right so um you know uh still
still working on my way through that um
but it it seems Seems promising there so
hopefully uh hopefully at some point
this is ready to use uh kind of directly
in Lucine there's a correspond issue on
uh on
solar and uh uh Joe buram says that that
you can also do this in uh uh inv vesa
so if uh so if you're using vesa too uh
you can add a a custom Searcher
implementation that uh uh applies
L all right how am I doing on time ah
there'll be uh there'll be sufficient
time for questions um in summary uh
adaptive reranking uh we find that this
improves the quity of search results at
uh at a pretty minimal cost so uh by
kind of leveraging offline computation
and this idea that similar documents are
close to one another we're able to
improve the quality of search results
find more of the relevant documents uh
basic with adding almost almost no
overhead uh it works for both uh rankers
and retrievers and it's ready to use
with uh with open source tools I'd like
to thank my collaborators on many of
these works so Craig McDonald at
University of Glasgow Nia to at
University of Pisa uh rich kazley and
oir at at Georgetown University helped
collaborate on uh on many of these
projects uh so uh thank you and are
there any
questions
fantastic thank you Sean um I I just say
when you're talking about the getting
this into Lucine what you need is a
Lucine committer any Lucine committers
in the house sh he says are in the
corner but
yes there are some people here could
probably help with that which is one of
the wonderful things about this this
event so do we have any questions for
sha first one over here come to you a
bit
later first of hello first of all uh
thanks for the amazing talk really
inspiring um am I right that if I would
pick not bm25 for my domain maybe even
better one that retrieves the initial
docks I would even come higher in the in
the benchmarks right uh yes so let's see
if we go
back
oh excuse the scrolling here right so uh
kind of the the core results here with
with bm25 right so using just a simple
lexical search improving and and getting
better results uh but yeah no we've seen
that if you have a stronger initial
stage uh you still see you still see
improvements this is ultimately bounded
by how good your ranker is right uh so
in this work we're using monot T5
there's even better ones today that you
know distill down gp4 and stuff like
that so I imagine um uh I imagine you
could get even even higher and as you
find more better results hopefully that
helps you find even more of the results
too so I'd expect it to both go both up
and to the right uh using uh using other
better first
stages thank you so we've got a question
online um I'm going to ask you this but
we may also need a help of someone in
the room um why does Vesper need a
custom Searcher can rank profiles solv
it oh I think I think that's a that's a
question for for for Joe burer where is
Joe where are you Joe there you are okay
so I'm gonna take this to
Joe yeah thank you for a great talk SE
um yeah you cannot do like a you can do
a lot of different things in Vestal
ranking profiles for sure uh and you can
express um a sparse retrieval bm25 or
whatnot and then rerank using um an
Adaptive model but the logic of
reranking and then figuring out hey this
was a good hit and then expanding the
search that we face that requires a
custom logic which is invest by done in
a custom Searcher yeah
great that's dianis I think thank you I
hope that answers your question uh so
next coming over here to you
here thank you for the great talk um
maybe I missed something but I think you
mentioned at some point the cross
encoder as your
ranker and if that was the case it is
unclear to me how you build the graph of
products right so so the the question is
um you're using a cross encoder to score
and normally when you're building a a
graph that say you know these documents
or these products are similar to these
other ones you're using the same thing
that you're scoring to build up that
graph um yeah that's that's a detail I
gloss over so I apologize for that um
but it turns out it it doesn't matter so
much what you pick right so we tested
both using uh kind of lexical similarity
right so issuing the query um building
this offline but issuing the the
document as a as a Lex iCal query over
bm25 and uh semantic similarity so kind
of encoding them as dense vectors and
looking up documents that are similar
based on that uh it all seems to work
right so as long as there's some notion
that this document is similar to this
document this is a an idea in in
Academia that we call Corr relevance
right so a document that is relevant to
uh that is also relevant to the same
kinds of queries if you have some
connection like that to build this up uh
that's all you really need um maybe it's
even something like we haven't tested
this on web scale data or anything like
that but maybe it's something like link
structure right so you have uh you have
products that may be linked to other
products maybe you could use that
structure to say maybe this is something
else you'd like to look at if you think
this document is relevant so kind of
anything that can get at this uh you
know if you think this is relevant this
might also be a be a good thing to look
at that's a great question thank you so
uh we don't have any more questions
online at the moment so we have one more
here
yeah so first of all a great idea
something new I learned today so have
the F have a question in the first part
where you said you're using a cross
encoder and then say the cross encoder
is thring this this is the first gr
document and then applying a&n search
for that particular document to find the
similar documents are there any lessons
that you learned in terms of setting
thresholds for that particular like say
like only the top the top question
scores of this particular similar to
this particular document because like if
you do a k and search again it's going
to loads of documents and then that's
going to again hurt your like the final
grade of relevance right so is there any
Lessons Learned on that threshold levels
that you what you said for the a in
search yeah so we found that it's it's
largely robust to kind of the K that
you're using in your K&N right uh going
super low means it's not searching much
of anything right uh so you're not
really searching enough of the neighbors
so you don't want to set it to like one
um also yes if you set it to a thousand
or something now you're no longer
letting uh letting it explore to to new
areas right so yeah we found anything
kind of in the range there's a graph in
the paper but I think it was something
like anything in the range from like 4
to 16 neighbors per per document tends
to work out nicely um but that might
kind of vary on the domain and and
application and stuff too thank you
yep any more questions yes there's one
over
here all right um how many iterations do
you use do between retrieving reranking
retrieving
reranking right so um basically we we
test it off uh we tested this by kind of
setting a fixed budget so we say we're
we're willing to rerank a 100 documents
for instance right um and kind of the
iterative process is going batch by
batch uh when uh when doing this kind of
processing for a cross encoder you need
to batch these documents anyway you
can't uh you can't really encode 100 on
a on a regular siiz GPU
um uh directly so we just used the B
size we were already using to score the
documents which I believe was something
like 16 and then we just kind of
alternate between the two modes right so
initially you pull from the top results
from from bm25 you score those then you
look up the neighbors of those top
results score a batch of 16 from those
uh and then back to your initial ranking
right so anything that you haven't yet
scored from that initial set you go to
the next 16 and score there so kind of
alternate between those uh between those
two modes
does that make
sense okay
so okay do we have any any other
questions for Sean in the
room okay so next H stack we're
expecting implementations we like some
practical stories please absolutely yeah
but thank you very much Sean thanks